{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "The weather is good today, except in the ___.",
      "a": "west-north",
      "b": "south-west",
      "c": "east-south",
      "d": "south-north",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- The four cardinal directions are the directions of north, east, south, and west, commonly denoted by their initials: N, E, S, W.\n- The intermediate directions are north-east (NE), south-east (SE), south-west (SW), and north-west (NW).",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "To keep _________ hours makes you healthy, wealthy and wise.",
      "a": "small",
      "b": "little",
      "c": "some",
      "d": "good",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- To keep good hours: to perform the same activities at good times",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "One dollar is roughly ___ to one Australian dollar.",
      "a": "worthy",
      "b": "equivalent",
      "c": "necessary",
      "d": "available",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Be equivalent to something: with the same size/value/importance as something else",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can't get a good picture on my TV set. There is something ___ with it.",
      "a": "bad",
      "b": "matter",
      "c": "wrong",
      "d": "untrue",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Something wrong with sth or sb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Susan began looking for a winter job in September; she knows that the ___ bird catches the worm.",
      "a": "wise",
      "b": "shrewd",
      "c": "thoughtful",
      "d": "early",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- The early bird catches the worm (idiom)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The salary increase proposed by the company fell ___ of what we had expected.",
      "a": "short",
      "b": "equal",
      "c": "behind",
      "d": "down",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Fall short of: not reach a particular level",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is the ___ man to be influenced by power.",
      "a": "most healthy",
      "b": "last",
      "c": "weak",
      "d": "hardly",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- The last: the person or thing that comes after all the others",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "She had _________ reason to be satisfied.",
      "a": "any",
      "b": "each",
      "c": "every",
      "d": "all",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Every: used to refer to all the people or things in a particular group or all the parts of something.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I never dreamed that his statement would lead to such a ___ situation.",
      "a": "selfish",
      "b": "grave",
      "c": "punctual",
      "d": "capable",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Grave (adj): so serious that you feel worried",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Poverty is _________ to dishonesty.",
      "a": "better",
      "b": "worse",
      "c": "less",
      "d": "preferable",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Be preferable toÂ ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}